<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EAC3_P1_Ganan_Gonzalo</string>
    <string name="title_item_detail">Item Detail</string>

    <string name="australia_detail">Australia, officially the Commonwealth of Australia,
        is a sovereign country comprising the mainland of the Australian continent,
        the island of Tasmania, and numerous smaller islands. It is the largest country
        in Oceania and the worlds sixth-largest country by total area.
        The neighbouring countries are Papua New Guinea, Indonesia
        , and East Timor to the north; the Solomon Islands and Vanuatu to the north-east;
        and New Zealand to the south-east. The population of 26 million is highly urbanised
        and heavily concentrated on the eastern seaboard. Australia\'s capital is Canberra,
        and its largest city is Sydney. The country\'s other major metropolitan areas are
        Melbourne, Brisbane, Perth, and Adelaide.</string>

    <string name="estonia_detail">Estonia, officially the Republic of Estonia, is a country on the
        eastern coast of the Baltic Sea in Northern Europe. It is bordered to the north by the Gulf
        of Finland with Finland on the other side, to the west by the Baltic Sea with Sweden on the
        other side, to the south by Latvia (343 km), and to the east by Lake Peipus and Russia
        (338.6 km).The territory of Estonia consists of a mainland and 2,222 islands in the
        Baltic Sea, covering a total area of 45,227 km2 (17,462 sq mi), water 2,839 km2
        (1,096 sq mi), land area 42,388 km2 (16,366 sq mi), and is influenced by a humid
        continental climate. The official language of the country, Estonian, is the
        second-most-spoken Finnic language.</string>

    <string name="chile_detail">Chile, officially the Republic of Chile, is a South American
        country occupying a long, narrow strip of land between the Andes to the east and the
        Pacific Ocean to the west. It borders Peru to the north, Bolivia to the northeast,
        Argentina to the east, and the Drake Passage in the far south. Chilean territory
        includes the Pacific islands of Juan Fernández, Salas y Gómez, Desventuradas,
        and Easter Island in Oceania. Chile also claims about 1,250,000 square kilometres
        (480,000 sq mi) of Antarctica under the Chilean Antarctic Territory.</string>

    <string name="china_detail">China, officially the People\'s Republic of China (PRC),
        is a country in East Asia and the world\'s most populous country,
        with a population of around 1.428 billion in 2017. Covering approximately
        9,600,000 square kilometers (3,700,000 sq mi), it is the third or fourth
        largest country by total area. Governed by the Communist Party of China,
        the state exercises jurisdiction over 22 provinces, five autonomous regions,
        four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing),
        and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.</string>

    <string name="uganda_detail">Uganda, officially the Republic of Uganda ,
        is a country in East-Central Africa. It is bordered to the east by Kenya,
        to the north by South Sudan, to the west by the Democratic Republic of the Congo,
        to the south-west by Rwanda, and to the south by Tanzania. The southern part of the
        country includes a substantial portion of Lake Victoria, shared with Kenya and Tanzania.
        Uganda is in the African Great Lakes region. Uganda also lies within the Nile basin,
        and has a varied but generally a modified equatorial climate.</string>

    <string name="congo_detail">The Democratic Republic of the Congo, also known as DR Congo,
        the DRC, DROC, Congo-Kinshasa, or simply the Congo, is a country located in Central Africa.
        It was formerly called Zaire (1971–1997). It is, by area, the largest country in
        sub-Saharan Africa, the second-largest in all of Africa (after Algeria),
        and the 11th-largest in the world. With a population of over 84 million,
        the Democratic Republic of the Congo is the most populous officially Francophone country,
        the fourth-most-populous country in Africa, and the 16th-most-populous country in the world.
        Eastern DR Congo has been the scene of ongoing military conflict in Kivu, since 2015.</string>

    <string name="egypt_detail">Egypt, officially the Arab Republic of Egypt,
        is a country in the northeast corner of Africa, whose territory in the Sinai
        Peninsula extends beyond the continental boundary with Asia, as traditionally defined.
        Egypt is bordered by the Gaza Strip and Israel to the northeast, the Gulf of Aqaba
        and the Red Sea to the east, Sudan to the south, Libya to the west, and the Mediterranean
        Sea to the north. Across the Gulf of Aqaba lies Jordan, across the Red Sea lies
        Saudi Arabia, and across the Mediterranean lie Greece, Turkey and Cyprus,
        although none share a land border with Egypt.</string>

    <string name="india_detail">India, officially the Republic of India,
        is a country in South Asia. It is the seventh-largest country by area,
        the second-most populous country, and the most populous democracy in the world.
        Bounded by the Indian Ocean on the south, the Arabian Sea on the southwest,
        and the Bay of Bengal on the southeast, it shares land borders with
        Pakistan to the west China, Nepal, and Bhutan to the north; and Bangladesh
        and Myanmar to the east. In the Indian Ocean, India is in the vicinity of Sri Lanka
        and the Maldives; its Andaman and Nicobar Islands share a maritime border with
        Thailand and Indonesia.</string>

    <string name="portugal_detail">Portugal, officially the Portuguese Republic,
        is a country located mostly on the Iberian Peninsula in southwestern Europe.
        It is the westernmost sovereign state of mainland Europe, being bordered to
        the west and south by the Atlantic Ocean and to the north and east by Spain.
        Its territory also includes the Atlantic archipelagos of the Azores and Madeira,
        both autonomous regions with their own regional governments.</string>

    <string name="russia_detail">Russia, or the Russian Federation, is a transcontinental
        country in Eastern Europe and North Asia. At 17,125,200 square kilometres
        (6,612,100 sq mi), it is, by a considerable margin, the largest country
        in the world by area, covering more than one-eighth of the Earth\'s
        inhabited land area, and the ninth most populous, with about 146.79 million people
        as of 2019, including Crimea. About 77% of the population live in the western,
        European part of the country. Russia\'s capital, Moscow, is one of the largest cities
        in the world and the largest city in Europe.</string>

</resources>
